<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.gamecenter</id>
  <name>Kirigami Application</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Aplicació Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aplicació Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Εφαρμογή Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Aplicación en Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Applicazione in Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kirigami-toepassing</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kirigami-program</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Aplikacija Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kirigami-program</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Програма на Kirigami</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKirigami Applicationxx</name>
  <summary>A short summary describing what this software is about</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un resum curt que descriu què fa aquest programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Un resum curt que descriu què fa aquest programari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μια σύντομη περίληψη που περιγράφει αυτό το λογισμικό</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una breve descripción de para qué es este software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un breve riassunto che descrive ciò che fa l'applicazione</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een korte samenvatting die beschrijft waar deze software over gaat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Eit kort samandrag om kva programvara gjer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Kratek opis tega programja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En kort sammanfattning som beskriver vad programvaran är</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Коротке резюме щодо призначення цього програмного забезпечення</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA short summary describing what this software is aboutxx</summary>
  <metadata_license>A permissive license for this metadata, e.g. "FSFAP"</metadata_license>
  <project_license>The license of this software as SPDX string, e.g. "GPL-3+"</project_license>
  <developer_name>The software vendor name, e.g. "ACME Corporation"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">El nom del venedor del programari, p. ex. «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">El nom del venedor del programari, p. ex. «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="el">Το όνομα του προμηθευτή του λογισμικού π.χ. «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">El nombre del vendedor (como «ACME Corporation»)</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Il fornitore del software, ad esempio «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">De naam van de softwareleverancier, bijv. "ACME Corporation"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">Utviklaren av programvara, for eksempel «Firma AS»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Ime prodajalca programja npr. "ACME korporacija"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">Programvarans tillverkarnamn, t.ex. "ACME AB"</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Назва виробника програмного забезпечення, наприклад «ACME Corporation»</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxThe software vendor name, e.g. "ACME Corporation"xx</developer_name>
  <description>
    <p>Multiple paragraphs of long description, describing this software component.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Diversos paràgrafs amb una descripció llarga, que descrigui aquest component de programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Diversos paràgrafs amb una descripció llarga, que descrigui aquest component de programari.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Πολλές παράγραφοι μακροσκελών περιγραφών, που περιγράφουν αυτό το συστατικό λογισμικού</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Varios párrafos con una larga descripción de las partes que constituyen este software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Più paragrafi di una descrizione lunga, che descrivono questo componente software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Meerdere paragrafen met lange beschrijving, die deze softwarecomponent beschrijft.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Ei lang programskildring over fleire avsnitt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Več odstavkov dolgega opisa, ki opisuje to programsko komponento.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Flera stycken med lång beskrivning, som beskriver programvarukomponenten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Декілька абзаців повного опису цього компонента програмного забезпечення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxMultiple paragraphs of long description, describing this software component.xx</p>
    <p>You can also use ordered and unordered lists:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">També es poden usar llistes ordenades i desordenades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">També es poden usar llistes ordenades i desordenades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Μπορείς επίσης να χρησιμοποιήσεις ταξινομημένες και αταξινόμητες λίστες:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">También se pueden usar listas ordenadas o sin ordenar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Puoi anche usare delle liste, ordinate o meno:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">U kunt ook geordende en ongeordende lijsten gebruiken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Du kan òg bruka nummererte og unummererte lister:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Lahko uporabite urejene ali neurejene sezname:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Du kan också använda numrerade och punktlistor:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ви можете використовувати упорядковані і неупорядковані списки:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxYou can also use ordered and unordered lists:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Feature 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Característica 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característica 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικό 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Funcionalidad 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Funzionalità 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Functie 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Funksjon 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Funkcia 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Možnost 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Funktion 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість 1</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFeature 1xx</li>
      <li>Feature 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Característica 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característica 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικό 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Funcionalidad 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Funzionalità 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Functie 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="nn">Funksjon 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Funkcia 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Možnost 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Funktion 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість 2</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFeature 2xx</li>
    </ul>
    <p>Keep in mind to XML-escape characters, and that this is not HTML markup.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Tingueu present escapar els caràcters XML, i que aquest no són marcadors HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Tingueu present escapar els caràcters XML, i que aquest no són marcadors HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Σημείωσε οι χαρακτήρες να είναι XML-escpae, και ότι δεν πρόκειται για HTML markup.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Recuerde que debe «escapar» los caracteres XML y que esto no es lenguaje de marcado HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ricordati di usare i caratteri di escape XML, e che questo non è un marcatore HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bedenk dat XML-tekens een escape moeten hebben en dat dit geen HTML-markering is.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Bruk XML-escaping av spesialteikn, og hugs at dette ikkje er HTML-kode.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Ne pozabite na ubežne znake XML in da niso HTML markup.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kom ihåg att XML-undanta tecken, och att det här inte är HTML-taggar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Слід пам'ятати, що символи XML слід екранувати, і що це не зовсім розмітка HTML.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKeep in mind to XML-escape characters, and that this is not HTML markup.xx</p>
  </description>
</component>
